Wichita Falls Symphony records, Inclusive: circa 1962-1966
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Wichita Falls Symphony records
Inclusive: circa 1962-1966
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
3842
Wichita Falls Symphony Orchestra, Inc.
10 folders.
The Wichita Falls Symphony records contain correspondence, minutes, and bylaws about the Wichita Falls Symphony Orchestra.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
The Wichita Falls Symphony Records document the still-active Wichita Falls Symphony Orchestra Inc. in Wichita Falls, Texas, during the 1960s. Founded in 1947, the Wichita Falls Symphony Orchestra has consistently offered quality artistic concerts to North Texas. During the 1960s, the time period of this collection, the orchestra's board was concerned with something still familiar to musical groups: how to raise money to stay in operation. The minutes also describe the board's work to schedule concerts and fundraisers throughout the year. Through their hard work, the symphony continues to operate today, providing quality musical entertainment to the Wichita Falls community.
Scope and Content
The Wichita Falls Symphony records begin in 1962 and end in 1966. Records include correspondence about various events hosted by the orchestra, board meeting minutes, bylaws of the group, and lists of participants in the symphony orchestra.
Arrangement
The Wichita Falls Symphony records are organized in four series: I. Correspondence, II. Minutes, III. Bylaws, IV. Participant Lists. Original order and arrangement has been kept through this recent processing.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 3842. Acquired 0-00-00
Related Resources
Related references
"Stories: Joe Prothro Wichita Falls Symphony Endowment Fund." Wichita Falls Area Community Foundation. Accessed 2013 April 12.
Index Terms
Places
Wichita Falls (Tex.) -- History.
Subjects
Symphony orchestras -- Texas -- Wichita Falls.
Genres
By-laws.; Correspondence.; Minutes (Records)
- Correspondence, 1962-1966; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  This series contains various letters to and from board members and others about the activities of the Wichita Falls Symphony Orchestra. The series is in good condition.
  - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 1962-1966; 2
  This series contains minutes from the annual board meeting and the executive committee. The series is in average condition.
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bylaws, 1962; 3
  General condition: Excellent.
  This series contains legal documents about the organization's governance and organization. This series is in excellent condition.
  - Articles of Incorporation, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Participant Lists, circa 1962-1966; 4
  This series contains various lists of people who helped and/or participated in various events with the Wichita Falls Symphony. This series is in good condition.
  - Members and Musicians, circa 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)